<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A little about me, my passions, and projects on HR</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A little about me, my passions, and projects on HR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Overview</title>
      <link>/blogs/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/overview/</guid>
      <description>As a fan of brevity, here are the most important points summarised into the key bullets:
 Born in Hong Kong Grew up in South Africa Undergraduate studies in Germany Hoping to work in Emerging Markets Investments after my time at LBS Passionate about aviation and a Private Pilot since last year  A bit more detail: Born to a German family in Hong Kong, I spent the first six years of my life in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDP Per Capital Analysis</title>
      <link>/blogs/data_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/data_1/</guid>
      <description>Challenge 2:GDP components over time and among countries To look at the differences in GDP accross countries, we have focussed on Germany, India, and USA. In order to gain a better understanding of their components and trends, we have sorted, cleaned, and filtered the data before plotting the relevant data points in the charts that follow:
UN_GDP_data &amp;lt;- read_excel(here::here(&amp;quot;data&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Download-GDPconstant-USD-countries.xls&amp;quot;), # Excel filenamesheet=&amp;quot;Download-GDPconstant-USD-countr&amp;quot;, # Sheet nameskip=2) # Number of rows to skipTo make the data easier to handle, we have changed the figures, renamed the indicators and pivoted the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All things aviation</title>
      <link>/blogs/aviation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aviation/</guid>
      <description>What does Henry do in his free time? In 2019 I took the time to attack a &amp;ldquo;bucket list item&amp;rdquo; - my pilots license. Many months of hard work paid off and I consider this one of my greatest personal achievements. Now I just need to find the time..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>some other R homework</title>
      <link>/blogs/data_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/data_2/</guid>
      <description>back story here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
